Thank you for watching!
Thank you for watching
Good morning.
Good afternoon.
Good evening.
Can you see me?
I'm telling you.
So...
Today
HITOKA SAKAI Birthday Party Live Streaming
I, Hitoka Sakai, turned 22 years old!
Congratulations!
We are now distributing our fan club at the same time!
Fan ClubFan Club
I'm sorry I'm all up in here.
What?
You're the star.
I'm the main character.
I'm the main character today.
I wasn't the leading man.
You're the hero today.
The main character.
Because I'm the main character
I didn't feel like it's my birthday.
Yes, it is.
Yesterday, I said OK.
OK, OK, OK.
It was past midnight, and I was like, oh, oh, oh, it's my birthday.
Last year, I did the Dengri Dice and stuff like that,
I had a celebration and everything,
This year, no, I was moaning.
It was past midnight, and I got a line,
And my mom woke up,
She said, "Good morning or happy birthday,
I was like, "Oh, it's your birthday.
You came home late, right?
Yes, yes, yes.
And, you know, I was like...,
Okay, me,
Wait, wait, wait. Let's not talk about this.
I'm done,
I'll talk about it later.
It's a long story.
So, what's first?
Well, let's all make a toast!
Cheers!
Let's sing!Let's sing!
I have to be able to sing for the first time.
Shall we sing?
Yeah, I'll sing.
How was it? We all sing.
Okay, let's do the dance.
Happy birthday to you
Happy birthday Riakidokar
Happy birthday to you!
Thank you!
Nice!
That was fun!
I'm so excited!
Suddenly...
Pan-pan!
Ping-pong!
That was awesome!
Thank you, guys!
Thank you!
All right, let's go.
Cheers!
I hope you have more ready for us.
Even her in the new world.
I will strive to be an even better idol
I will strive to be even better every day.
Please keep up the good work!
And with that, I'd like to say
Cheers!Cheers!
Cheers!
Bon appétit.
Delicious.
Cold.
Delicious!
Delicious.
I'm gonna close.
Cheers. Cheers. Cheers.
Cheers.
Remember Chat?
Orange juice.
It's true.
Something official is up.
The official version?
It's official.
They saw the footage on TV.
It's true.
They made a cake and everything.
And celebrated.
And everything.
And all kinds of advertisements.
Thank you so much for all the points you've made.
Thank you very much.
It's my pleasure.
So, cake, you can have your cake and eat it too, right?
Cake? Oh, yeah, that's right.
We have sweets, too.
We have plastic matches.
Can I get you anything?
I love these.I love these.
Do you love gummy bears?
Oh, Hito-chan makes me smile.
It's true.
Cute!
So cute!
Wait, is this mango?
It's a mango.
What? Why?
Oh, my God, I'm so happy.
Mangos are delicious.
No way. Mango.
Mango's good. Mango.
Hey, what's up? What's up?
Cake. Yay.
Yay. Yay. Looks good.
Cake. Cake. Cake.
That's pretty.
Cake. Cake.
Good night, sweetheart.
Oh, my God.
It's super cute.
Thank you.
You put my name in the name box.
It's not strawberry, is it?
That's for sure.
Hey, I thought it was great.
We were just talking about not being strawberries.
Mango.
It's a miracle.
I'm so happy.
Looks delicious.
I haven't had much mango cake.I haven't had much mango cake.
Can I have a mango?
Until the other day.
Mario used to eat mango every day.
You've been asleep.
Mango is good.
Let's eat.
Bon appétit.
From the hero.
Bon appétit!
Oh, it's so cute!
Cute.
Oh, wow.
Oh, it's gone. Are you okay?
Are you okay?
Wide chocolate.
Was it this good?
It's delicious.
Wide chocolate.
Thank you for the food.
Bon appétit!
What is it, everyone?
Oh, my God, what kind of cake is this?
Chef M is coming out.
Oh, that's nice.
This looks delicious.
Yum. - Yum.
Yummy?
Bon appétit.
Wow, it looks so good!
The cream inside is mild and delicious!The cream inside is mild and delicious!
Delicious!
Refreshing!
Azatoito-chan is the one from Ponkuro.
Cute
Delicious!
Very tasty!
So delicious!
Happy?
Cheese cream?
Not sweet cream.
It's delicious.
Strawberry mille-feuille.
Fruit tart.
Homemade strawberry tart.
Oh, my God.
Ern, please.
Here you go.
It's kind of refreshing.
Delicious.
Ern, please.
It's delicious.
Want some?
What did you see?
Is it good?
Too much?
You drink too much.
It's good.
I'm so happy.
Oh, my God.Oh, my God.
This is delicious.
Delicious.
Easy to eat
Beautiful layers
Might be the first time I've heard it described in this way
It's never too sweet
Insanely beautiful
Delicious!
I'm eating it the same way so much
Delicious.
It's scrub time for all of you!
All part 1
All part...
The whole story.
I mean, they want to see screentime everywhere they go.
Really.
But cute.
I remember something. It's good, right?
Yum!
Baked Cheesecake
I want a baked cheesecake.
That would be awesome.
She's commenting on how long her hair is.
Good morning. - Good morning.
Look how long my hair is.
Is it long?
It's really long.
It's grown long.
I really like to go to Make-up Tan twice a week or once a week.I really do have a taste for make-up tans, maybe twice a week or once a week.
I'm looking forward to seeing you every time.
Then they say, "It's grown!
They say, "It's grown forever!
It's so fast.
But it's really this delivery.
I think I'll wear it at that time, until about this time.
Up to this point.
But during this tour, I'm thinking of stretching it a little bit.
Don't wear it until the end of the tour.
How far do you have to wear it?
That's right, that's right, that's right.
What?
No, thank you.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
It'll grow.
It'll grow another two inches.
Yeah.
Interesting.
Two centimeters.
About five centimeters.
All the way down to my waist.
Yeah, it's delicious.
Who's the hardest worker in the group?
Who is it?
You scared the shit out of me.
I look like a beaver.
The one in the back,
Don't cut me off!
It's Mr. Tanami,
Mr. Tanami is waiting for you.
Thank you very much.
Oh!
Oh, but it's a little bit like this.But, I don't know, it's a little bit like this.
Foreground, a little foreground...
Ha-ha-ha-ha...
Just barely, just barely
Just barely bear with it, just barely.
Okay, let's go next.
Yes, let's go next.
Yes, let's go next
Let's have a good time again, and enjoy it later.
Now for the next project.
Let's start Hito-chan's Birthday Question!
So, to the questions we received from everyone
Pappa-pappa-pappa-pappa-pappa-pappa-pappa-pappa!
sent to a lot of people.
Yes, there are more!
Yes, let's go then!
Let's go poof poof poof.
Yes, sir.
Let's see.
It's from Moe. Thank you very much.
If Hito-chan were to design a costume
what kind of costume would you like to make?
Hmmm...
A backless costume.
Definitely.
Yes. Yes.
Okay.
All six of us will be wearing them, by the way.
I see. I see.
And yet, I'm afraid the members won't like it.
Well, they might hate me a lot when I'm in my solo outfit.
I don't know, but...
I don't know, but... you know, a lot of Tokimake products have one-piece skirts or something like that.I don't know, I guess there are a lot of one-piece skirts made in Japan at the time.
Yeah.
Or something like a pudding skirt.
It's cute, isn't it?
And then there's...
I wonder...
I don't know, it's just too much right now.
There's so many outfits I want to try on.
I'd like to wear right now.
The only costume I want to wear is the one with the open back.
Let's do it some other time.
Okay, well, I can zip up your footprints.
Whenever you're ready.
Whatever you're in the mood for.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I can leave it so you can zip it up.
I don't mind being zipped up.
It's not very revealing.
The moment I turned my back
They were all inside.
That's interesting.
Yeah, it is.
But I was like...
I'd like to dress like a K-pop idol.
I'd personally like to wear one.
That's what I've always wanted to do.
Denny...
Open your back.
Hey, you know what?
Now, let's continue.
What is your favorite strawberry food in the world?
What do you like best?
From Milpyong.
Food made with strawberries.Strawberry food.
They're delicious, aren't they? Lupi strawberries.
Oh, they're delicious. They're simply delicious.
Delicious, but...
But... I don't know.
Food made with strawberries.
Not just strawberries.
I'm in a juicy mood
But strawberry millefeuille is so good.
Me, I think I'd get tired of that.
It's Kehachi!
Kehachi's strawberry millefeuille is so delicious.
I think I like it.
They targeted your millefeuille?
I guess so.
Is that right?
I love strawberry milk too.
I love strawberry milk.
It's so good!
It's a little bit cold, but it's good.
But it's like... what's it called?
It's from a little high-end supermarket.
It's pink.
Pink.
Strawberry, like strawberry milk you can make at home.
Mm-hm-hm.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, like strawberry milk you can make at home with milk.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm, mm-hmm
Ichibiko
Ichibiko.
No, I mean, a little more than Ichibiko.
Yeah.
Yeah, I like that a lot.Yes, I like that a lot.
I like it a lot.
Go on, then.
Ready, Shinko?
Oh, me?
No?
What were you doing the moment you turned 22?
Strawbilly.
As I was telling you earlier.
Yesterday, I was lying around and I was thinking...
Every time I get older
I feel like every time I get older
I'm getting less and less passionate
I'm getting less and less enthusiastic about my birthday.
It's getting worse.
I need to turn it up.
That's... no... no...
When I was little, my family would have a big party.
My grandma would come over.
I don't know...
I said, "I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I thought it would be a waste
I thought, "What a waste!
So, you know. So, no.
Well, the moment it's more of a birthday moment, I'd like to try my hand at something more, wouldn't you?
Yes, something understandable.
We're all gonna watch?
That's nice.
Will you do that?
You want to?
Yeah, it's good.
You're gonna do it.I know you do.
I really peed with my own eyes yesterday.
It's a glass can.
Come on, next time.
It'll be nice. You'll meet Leo.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Can we stop now?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
In a minute.
Soon.
Right now.
Yeah, I don't think I can teach you.
But, you know, I wanted to bring Leo if that was okay.
Uh-oh.
I might not make it.
Okay, then, continue.
What would you like to try in your 22nd year?
Please tell us why. From Mr. Halpin.
I want to ride in a balloon.
Oh, I want to ride!
I want to ride! I want to ride!
What's that? What?
I want to go on a balloon ride.
I always wanted to go on a balloon last year.
I've never been able to get a chance to go on a balloon ride.
I want to go on a balloon ride.
I also want to dye my hair.
Ahhh...
I finally have one.
I want to dye my hair.
Yes, I would like to dye my hair.
I'd like to do that.
I also want to start eating spicy food
Something tastySomething delicious.
If there are more things to eat...
The more delicious things you can eat, the more delicious things you can feel.
You know...
It's not enough.
So, then, do you have any special goods that you use on a daily basis?
Oh, you have an air punch case? Oh, you have one, don't you?
I haven't gotten a new one yet.
Oh, yeah, I'm still using the old one, the good one.
I want that one. The fan.
Oh, yes, the Fabryn fan.
Yes, yes, a Fabryn fan.
Fabryn? Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, the Fabryn fan is really cute.
I was thinking maybe I would have carried it around with me.
I think so.
It's from Mr. Swore.
Thank you very much.
Thank you.
Take me home soon.
Tell me what you used to do.
Well, what did you do?
I've never heard of it.
That's it, isn't it?
Dancing for a day.
Dance for a day?
Dancing all day?
What was that you were learning?
I think it was a trial lesson.
Trial lesson?
Trial lessons for a year?
My friend asked me to dance because she wanted to.
I couldn't do it, so I quit.
And the pool?And the pool?
The breaststroke incident.
When I grew up and went on dates.
My dad told me it was a little weird to date in a crawl
I did my best in the pool, even the breaststroke.
And then there's rhythmic gymnastics.
I've heard of rhythmic gymnastics.
I did it for six years.
I don't know what else I did.
I really don't remember.
I don't.
Maybe there's that much to get used to.
I like to dance all day.
One day at a time times.
Something like that.
Right, and then there's the other thing.
I feel like I'm still dancing all day
Yeah, I guess I still dance all day.
So I'm still dancing, and I'm still shocked that I'm dancing.
I'm shocked that I'm still dancing.
I wonder why I'm dancing.
Yes, I do.
And Cherry seems to enjoy dancing a little bit.
Yes, she is.
She's been going to some kind of parent-child cooking teacher.
What?
Like a cooking teacher you go with your mom.
Yeah, I went to a lot of those.
I have to tell you something now. In front of me.
Isn't this it?
Dance.
It's not dancing.
It's not a dance.
Dance.Dance
Thank you from Aisan
Miss Ai
Follow up.
If we had a project where we could take only one member to a deserted island for a week of camping.
Who would you take?
Takumi.
What?
What will work?
Will it work?
Are you bad at this?
No, I'm not.
I don't know.
He brings me pinecones.
He's had experience with pinecones.
He's been there.
Camping experience.
Yeah, I'm kind of, I'm kind of, Junior's like, okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay.
Yeah, yeah.
Oharu, you know, you're a booger.
Ouch.
Don't bug me.
I know.
But Parta is the one who seems to be the most happy when I make food.
And Aki-chan, anyway, she seems to be cheerful and will stay next to you.
Plain and simple.
I'm going to make it a level playing field.
That's right.
She's curious, so I think she'll have a good time.
Pio, he's kind of like that...
Oh.
Pio.Pio.
Pio?
I don't care what it is.
He's gonna turn everything into something fun.
He'll turn anything negative into something fun.
So I'm gonna go with Pio.
Yay.
Let's go to a deserted island.
I want to go to a deserted island.
I want to go.
Just a little bit further.
Let's go get a balloon.
There's no way we can get a balloon from a deserted island.
I don't think so.
Pio.
Go on, how much more can you read?
Almost there?
Thanks to TN for my latest favorite haircut!
My latest haircut?
It's a recent one.
The latest one?
Yeah.
Oh!
Straight down.
That's good.
It's kind of long.
It's prettier.
Straight and grated.
I think. I think so.
Straight.Straight.
I'm curling it today.
Let's continue.
If you and Hachitaro were to collaborate on YouTube.
What would you like to do?
June's.
Thank you, June's.
We talked about it a lot, didn't we?
We talked about it. You know, we talked about the bullet train.
The bullet train?
Yeah, you said it was right next to you.
Oh, yeah, yeah, something like that.
I got a little raw.
I'm baking.
Grilling.
We talked the whole time.
We talked forever.
I don't know if I'm allowed to talk like that.
I don't know if I'm allowed to talk like this.
I wondered if I could talk with the staff.
I wondered if Oharu wanted to go to bed.
But we got so excited, didn't we?
Yes, we did.
It was fun.
No, no.
No, it wasn't.
We had a good time.
That's not why I wanted to go to bed.
That's right, that's right.
That's when we talked.
Oharu loves ramen, right?
So I asked her to bring me her favorite ramen recommendation.
And we ended up eating it while we were eating it.
Yes, I was saying, if you like me, I'm all about spicy food.Yeah, I was saying, if you like me, it's all pretty spicy.
Of course you do.
It's pretty painful, isn't it?
I recommend it.
Oh, I see. I'll look for it.
I'll look for it. I'd like to do some.
Okay, when it gets a little more painful.
Not right now.
I'm feeling a little hot and bothered right now.
It's hard.
It's a little bit difficult, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Okay, let's do the last one.
Last one.
That's right.
Okay, Rust...
Last.
When did Takemi become your hobby?
[Comment] From Hotel Kikuchi! Thank you!
Well, I mean, I've always been camping since I was in elementary school.
I mean, I've been camping more than I've been staying at inns or hotels.
Hmmm...
It's like, "Dad, if you're off already, why don't you go with someone else?
Yeah, you know, just the two of us.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I've always liked it more than when I started.
Even recently, I've been doing it by myself.
Now that I'm an adult, I'm thinking of doing it by myself.
You want to start by yourself?
All of it?
Why are you sneaking around in there?
What's number two?
Julia.
Oh, I'm going to get quiet.Oh, I'm so squeamish.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I'm calling Julia.
I don't know who you're going to call Number Two.
I'm going to call Julia.
What are you calling her?
You scared me.
Something in my ear to Julia.
To Julia.
I'm going to do it to Julia.
I know.
I was with my family.
With your family?
Yeah, I was with my family.
Oh, you're doing it with your family.
Before that...
I went with Fuku-chan's family and Namin alone.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
You let them play with you
Yeah, it was a lot of fun.
It was so much fun!
It was like we knew each other.
My family and my neighbor's family were there with us.
And they made it a mystery, too.
It was so much fun.
So, thank you very much for your support.
Thanks a lot, everyone!
I'm sorry I couldn't read them all.
But I'm glad. Thank you.
Thanks a lot.
Who sings best, by the way?
Oh, that's right, that's right.
Well, here are the results.Now, let's announce the results
Results
First of all, let's see which was which.
First place
From 5th place
Fifth place
From the fifth place.
I already know.
Fifth place goes to Aki-chan.
Fifth place goes to Nee-chan.
I'm so happy.
That's what I'm talking about.
I called you as soon as I woke up.
When I woke up, it was 7:25.
Wow.
That's what I thought.
Wake up.
I was awake.
And then something happened.
I didn't transform then.
I was sleepwalking.
What was that, 7:25? I thought it was right on time for my birthday.
I thought it was great.
And then there was a little note that made me happy.
You said it made you happy.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
And number four is...
This one.
It's late at night.
It was 10:30.
10:30.
I took a bath yesterday.
I started taking a bath at 11:45.I started taking a bath at 11:45.
Then I saw that the time in the bath was off by 30 minutes.
I remembered why I could afford this.
I was doing lulu lulu.
I was just a little bit too comfortable with it all.
It's always easier to play in the bath.
The bath is
And the sign is
That's good.
HACHANGO
Yay!
That's great.
Third place. It says Rage Lake.
That's right.
It's Rage Lake.
Oh, my gosh.
That was fast.
Late.
That's unusual.
Yes, it is.
Oh, really?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
I see.
Then I'm super confident.
Oh, I'm super, super confident.
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Oh, my God.
What?
Really.
Really?
No, really.No, already.
No, really.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
Which one?
Which is...
I don't know.
No, it's me.
By the way.
Who came in first?
Oh, it's me already.
Set the time for 55 minutes.
I've been ready for five minutes.
By the way.
I was really counting down.
You know, with the joker in first place.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
You can do it.
I can do it.
Let's go.
Okay, we'll start with first place.
First place.
First place goes to...
Healin!
I don't know what's wrong with me.
But...
But, but...
This...
It's really good.
It was really great.
It was a great fight.
I was going to send you another one, but I decided not to.
It would change the order.Because the order would change.
Ah.
That's enough to think about.
I challenged him when it was over.
It's amazing.
Comment and start.
Pinging at the same time.
Sorry, the temperature difference here is amazing.
My sweet potato daughter and I.
I'm so happy.
Thank you.
You're so cute.
Thank you very much.
But the members were all really fast.
I was happy.
Well, let's go.
Let's go.
It looks like we'll be able to see the Gunplug chat.
Tickets are first-come, first-served.
I just got the last one,
I'm not going.
Cute guy.
I can't get enough.
Look at that.
That was a hell of a fight.
Peaceful conflict.
It's amazing.
I'm so happy for you.
For me.
I don't remember it being this long.
What's the matter?
There's still some left.
I think I'll send it a little early.I think I'll send it a little early.
I was thinking
about...
By the way, I had a friend who grinded.
Oh, it's really
That's great.
I can see a little bit.
Impressions are being stretched, to add
Subtle.
I'm calling you sweet potato girl, not juliaci girl.
LOL!
Baya-chan got me.
We all fought over it and did it every day.
The biggest fight in the family.
Hey, everyone was really
They're all fighting over each other.
You're so happy.
I'm so happy.
You guys did a great job celebrating.
Thank you so much.
It's so exciting.
I'm so happy for you.
And so is my body.
What do you mean, you look so cute from down here?
I've been wondering if you're okay.
I'm fine. I'm fine.
Are you okay around here?
You're cute.
If you write that I'm gaining weight.
I'm gonna stop streaming this.
You understand?
Congratulations.
I congratulated you.
Thank you.Thank you.
I'm already 22. I'm so happy.
Oh, my God, Aki-chan's an orange one too.
So cute, so cute, so cute.
I wanted to send one myself.
What? I wanted to send you a message too.
Don't you know Aki-chan's LINE? Everyone.
What? You don't know?
You don't know?
Aki-chan also has TikTok.
It's cushion time.
No, no, no.
What's more?
Quickly?
Quicker?
Come on, come on.
You guys are on Twitter.
It's gonna be great!
Birthday line exchange.
Great. I'll have to hold off on the next one.
Yeah, I'll do that.
Let's get a new one.
Let's get a birthday account.
That's great.
Let's make one.
We can make an account where everyone can see what we're up to.
Thank you, guys.
I hope you guys keep Twitter alive and kicking after this.
See you later.
Let's go to the next one.
Next up.
HITO-chan is the star of the show.
We've been waiting for you.I've been waiting for you.
what is it?
What is it?
First of all... for now...
Let's start with the raw photos.
Let's start with the raw photos...
You know... she's really cute.
Seriously, this time.
When we took this picture...
Acchan...
She took this picture of me.
She took this really cute picture of me.
I couldn't take it anymore.
I've been recording it ever since the day we took it.
That's right.
You're so cute.
I've told you this story a million times.
Here they are... the raw photos.
This way.
Dren.
She's so cute.
Can we get a picture of that?
She's super cute.
Oh, my God, she's so cute.
Oh, doll.
She's super cute.
That's amazing.
Fresh.
So cute.
I'm going to get all of them!
Here's one with a kiss.
I got a kiss. One.
I kissed you.I kissed him.
Oh, he's so cute.
He's so cute.
Look.
Three hundred and eighty-eight thousand.
What?
He's so cute.
Cute.
Lips.
This beautiful outfit.
She's so cute.
She's a young lady!
She's got rhinestones under her eyes.
Oh, yeah.
She's so cute!
She's so cute.
So cute!
This is so cute!
This is cute.
So cute!
So cute.
I love it. It's like a little magical girl.
Puella Magi is awesome.
So cute.
We all want to kiss.
I do.
That's so cute.
Oh, my God!
I'm so happy!Wow, I'm so happy!
So cute!
You're gonna want to get one of these!
This is what you get when you go to a place like this.
What's this?
Ribbons. Ribbons.
Ribbons.
So cute.
It's all so pretty.
I'm so happy.
It's so cute.
Isn't it pretty?
Your hands are fresh.
They're fresh.
Guys, by the way, the dupe herself...
I'm writing a comment.
I wrote a comment.
Oh, really?
Gentlemen.
That's right.
I wrote them.
Um, please find it.
By all means, by all means.
Yes, sir.
And the top of the head
Oh!
La-la-la-la-la-la-la-la-la...
Ta-da!
Oh, wow!
It's so cute! It's so nice!
So cute!
It's so cute!
Pierfull is always so cute!Pierfull is always so cute.
Eh, cute.
She's a doll.
Cute!
My favorite!
Oh-kun
Okun
Cute...just like an AI.
The perfume key is something,
That's the one I'm interested in.
Oh, that guy!
What's that?
What's this?
There's the original kanpachi.
I was looking forward to seeing what it is this year.
First of all, a pretty person or this,
Shaban-dama.
Name.
Name match.
Everyone belongs to Hito-chan.
Please write everyone's name.
I'm not good at remembering, so this is how I'll remember.
That's so good!
Oh, yeah
This way.
Don't show them this.
Did I show it to you?
I think I got everyone's picture taken.
But I hope it's okay.
I think it's fine.
You see this?
It's got a QR code on it, and it's got a video that only the winner gets to see.
That's nice.Nice!
So this is a video that only the winner can see.
I hope you all put it up somewhere.
Oh, wow!
I made it.
It's not very short.
It's not on line.
Oh, it's not a line.
I'll pass that around, too.
LINE?
I'll pass it around.
Let's go.
LINE?
Let's go!
Let's go this way.
Great. It's nice.
It's all good, right?
Yeah, it's all good. And the last one, the last one.
I'm curious about that.
Wow, there it is!
Ha-ha-ha.
What's that?
Good job Hito-chan, you're the king.
We wrote it.
It's packed, isn't it?
Crammed... into one sheet.
That's right.
All of you...
When I was King Hito-chan...
I asked you to write a pretty picture of me.
I said...
At that time...At that time...
You drew this.
It's a portrait of me.
It's very rare.
Please get that one.
What will you put on the sign from below?
What kind of sign are you going to put up?
It's cute.
I wonder if it's a group of coins. So many personalities.
It's amazing. It's like they're all drawn by different people.
It's not the same person at all.
Cute. We've seen this before, right?
Pando. That's it. Maybe there's a Calumet girl too.
He's so cute!
We're always together. The one who watches.
It's on the bed, too.
We have other badges, too. So cute!
Please get one!
Yes, sir.
Yes, and then...
Oh, yes! Ladies and gentlemen.
Ta-da!
We are pleased to announce the release of
Vol. 2 release!
Yay!
Yay! Yay!
Last time it was necklaces.
I want to call you!
You don't want to call Julia, do you?
Her name's Julia.
Julia is a stronger name.I think the name Julia is stronger than the name Julia.
I wish I could call you!
Mr. Mass.
Julia.
Julia?
No Julia.
It was fun.
And this one called Oharu...
I'm not Haru, I'm Hacha.
Hacha-hacha.
It's a dance and it's smooth.
I said Hachan.
Would you like to hear Tetsuya's pad?
Uh, um...
Phone call
Um, I'm sorry. I changed it with the name of the parent who became me, you know.
That's right.
Everyone, Volume 2 is coming out, so please look forward to it.
Let's fight!
All the time!
I'll have Hachitaro appear again.
Let Hachitaro make an appearance.
Now then, let's move on to today's main point.
This time,
Yes, I'm going to say it this time. I'm going to say it first,
I did it this time.
Did I say that? I have to say it.
I sang this time, too.
I sang it, and I did it.
I'm sure many of you may have guessed it.
I love it! That one!
That one! That's it!
I think,
It's the most difficult thing I've ever sung in my life.That one is really the most difficult one I've ever sung in my life.
I said I'm going to do this one already,
I was thinking of quitting.
It was really too difficult.
It was at the level of respect,
I wondered if anyone could sing this.
But I did my best and sang it in my own way,
Please listen to it.
Let's go, shall we?
Arasumeri with an invincible smile
Mysterious, mysterious, I want to know your secret
Even the way you're pointing at me is her area
You're a perfect liar
You're a genius, you're a genius, you're a genius
Oh my sweet girl, you're my sweet girl
What did you eat? What's your favorite book?
Where do you go for fun?
Haven't you eaten anything? Don't tell me that.
No matter what they ask you, you just go along with it.
So matter-of-factly, but with a hint of acidity
Ideal and invisible is the taste of honey
No such thing, no such thing, no such thing, no such thing, no such thing, no such thing
The pipe you like is the pipe they like, so go ahead, answer me.
I don't know what it's like to love someone
I don't know.
I don't know if it's true or false
I don't know if it's true or false I'll fall for one more person
I'll make you fall in love with me again
You'll make everyone fall in love with you
You're the perfect idol, the ultimate idol
Golly's idol appears
The reincarnation of the first star
Ah, I love you with that smileAh, I love you with that smile
I'll make everyone fall in love with me
Ah, with your eyes, even if your words are a lie
It's perfect love
Yes, she's special
We're a bonus from the flowers
We're the stars' extras
It can't be all because of her
There's no such thing as jealousy and envy.
No way. This is not a story.
That's why I can't forgive her. She's not perfect.
I can't forgive you. I can't forgive myself.
You're stronger than anyone I've ever met, and I'll never accept that.
You're the one that everyone wants to believe in.
You're the strongest, the most powerful, the most invincible idol of all.
Justin's the best of them all
Melia with her signature smile
The only secret I'll keep from you is this one
I love you, Kalia, I spin it with a lie
This is my own kind of love
Even the sweat that runs down my face is beautiful aqua
This eyelid that hides the ruby
I am Maria, dancing around the stage
Yes, a lie is the best kind of love
I've never been loved by anyone, never loved anyone
I've never been loved by anyone, I've never loved anyone, I believe that one day this lie of mine will become true
Someday I'll have it all I'm such a greedy idol
What do you want? I want to be right about the dynamite.
I want to be right
I'll lie again today
I hope that one day these words will be true
But I still couldn't tell you and you alone
Ah, I can finally say
I'm not lying, I love youThis is not a lie. I love you.
My savior, my true savior, my savior
I love it.
That's my super idol.
But you look good in red.
It looks good on you because it suits you.
It looks good on you because you look like you're wearing red.
It's so difficult.
No matter how many times I practiced at karaoke,
I couldn't get it right at all,
I thought it might not work,
But somehow I managed to keep at it.
There were a lot of high parts,
There were a lot of high places and a lot of rapping,
I had to get good at it.
But I really wanted to sing, so I did my best.
I did my best.
How did you like it?
I really wanted you to sing.
Hey, I've heard you want to sing.
From the very beginning when this song came out.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
So, uh, when is it coming up?
I worked really hard to sing it.
After this...
I'm going to upload it on YouTube, the official YouTube channel of Chotokimeki-incentive.
It will be uploaded on YouTube, the official YouTube channel of Chotokimeki Incentive,
Please watch it over and over and over again.
Please watch it as many times as you can.
Yes, that's good.
I'm glad.
The response has been great.
It's hard work.
Yes, something like that, Ai-chan, um, pull over,Yes, something like that, Ai-chan, um, pull it over,
I want to tie my hair back, too.
I did a lot of pulling.
Okay, that's all for now.
I'll be on the Hit Channel later today with my weekly update.
I'm updating every week.
Today, I'm going to be updating every Thursday.
Today, I'll be updating YouTube on the same day today.
This time
It's a very long video, about 45 minutes long.
It's my birthday, so I shot a lot of stuff.
Um, it's kind of just the first opening.
Well, this is the thumbnail of that one.
Just a little bit of the opening, just a little bit of the opening, just a little bit of the opening, just to play it.
Ah!
You know...
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Hey.
Let's see if it plays.
I'm traveling with Leo. Yay!
I'd like to take a bath.
That's great.
Here we go. Pack.
Ta-da! Eels. Eels and eggs?
I changed my hair.
Good night.
I went on a trip with Miya-kun. Two days and one night.
Oh, well, is there a hot spring scene? No?
No? No, not that one.
That one? What?
I can see it.
What's that?
Worst case scenario, it's the group's here.
Um...Um...
Huh?
I'm not saying there isn't.
So, um, everyone, after this,
I'll be opening the premiere at 9:00 p.m,
If I have time, I'll join the chat,
I'll join in the chat, so I'm sorry if it's too late.
So please come and see it. I'm sorry if it's not ready yet, but please take a look.
It's a birthday special. Please watch a lot.
That's all for now,
Dashimaro's Corner.
Yes, that's it. I'm looking forward to the next one, I am.
Next, Hito-chan's present is Ryuto.
Well then, let's collect the dake once here.
Are you collecting?
I think I'm going to find a lot of things.
Oh, this is Yuri's, isn't it?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
What, what, what?
May I?
Close your eyes.
That's definitely the one.
You want to see the shime-chan?
I saw a little bit.
Oh, here.
So you'll leave the cake to me?
No, I don't think so.
Shime-chan's better.
I got it.
This is mine.
This is Akitan.
This is her.
Oh, sorry.Oh, sorry.
Not at all. Here.
Oh, it's the least I can do.
But if you look at me...
This is Hitotan's.
You're beautiful.
You're so beautiful.
Isn't it beautiful?
This will be over soon.
Yes, sir.
Then we'll have to play rock-paper-scissors-scissors.
That's right.
Oh, let's put it on the front side.
Eh, thanks.
I've helped you out again.
No problem.
Let's play rock-paper-scissors-scissors.
The winner goes first.
First one is "goo" rock-paper-scissors.
First, go-janken-po (rock-paper-scissors-scissors rock-paper)
Rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors
First, goo rock-paper-scissors, rock-paper-scissors.
Oh, first one.
Wait a minute.
Rock, paper, scissors, rock, paper, scissors.
Number three?
I'm trying so hard.
Number one.
Okay.
Okay, I'll go first.
Okay, then.
Please open this one.
Here you go.
Okay, thank you very much.Yes, thank you.
What is it?
What does it smell like?
What is it? In the back?
I'm not sure of the specifics.
Yes, this is...
It's herbal tea.
I'm so happy.
Oh, my gosh!
I love this herbal tea!
This is a herbal tea called "Strongest Me"!
What?
The strongest me!
Yes, you see, the name is...
The moment I saw the name, I was so excited
So I chose this herbal tea.
Thank you.
It's a little bit different from the other ones,
Orange peel,
Ginger..,
Oh, there's ginger.
Lovers' Hit Cinnamon. Oh, there's cinnamon.
It's got cinnamon.
Oh, my gosh.
Yeah, it's something, you know, you can drink a few cups of it.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Here you go, and here you go.
This one is pretty much the main one.
I had decided to have this one, too.
Thank you very much.thank you
what is it?
thank you
Thank you.
Congratulations.
Thank you
Thank you.
It wasn't there.
Congratulations.
Thank you. Thank you.
I feel like a tomboy.
I don't know...
I don't know
We're not...
Are you with me?
Oh?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
You look happy.
Okay, let's cut.
Yay!
Next, we have throat black rice!
Hito-chan-chan and I were talking about how much we love throat blackfish,
So when I found this at the restaurant, I knew I had to have it.
It's kind of instant,
Instant?
A rice cooker.
It's a rice dish made in a rice cooker.
Wow, it's really good.
It's good.
Thank you.
It's a restaurant that serves really good snacks and rice accompaniments.It's a restaurant that serves really good snacks and rice accompaniments.
Heh.
I bought it there. The rice with rice.
Thank you very much. It's definitely delicious.
There were various kinds of rice. Like the tiger globefish rice.
Wow, that's something nice.
That's nice.
I decided to make omochora.
Thank you very much. It's delicious.
As expected.
Akito, you're ready too.
First place baby.
Thank you.
Yes.
Then, let's continue.
Yes, we'll go on.
Okay, next is Julian. Yes, this way.
Okay, let's see.
This is Mike from someone's drawing, isn't it?
Yes, it is. I'm, uh... I'm rooting for you.
Really? You have a rooting interest in me?
Well, I thought, "Well, Julian's in first place, so I'll draw his face.
I did.
What is this?
Well, well, the main one.
You should definitely see it.
You're right. Sorry.
Oh, sorry. Put it in.
Oh, sorry.
All right.
Okay, bye.
Oh, my God, what is that?
Is it over there? That way.
Oh, my God.Oh.
Is this Ren's?
Len's present.
Here we go.
It's either a little or a lot.
Yeah, I guess so.
You think it'll fit?
What?
Isn't this a little tiny?
It's not tiny.
Oh, it's fine.
Is it a hat? The other way around? Yes.
A hat! Cute!
A hat!
Hat! Cute!
Oh, my God!
You know what?
We, uh...
We had hats, you know, when we were camping and stuff.
Yeah, with a guy.
If we went camping or something...
You know...
Leo and Hitaka would have matching hats.
I think it would be really cute.
You mean you can pull the ears out from the side?
Yes.
For Leo.
I'm sure he'd look great in it.
I think he's absolutely adorable.
I'll get a picture.
Send them to me too.
I'll send you a picture.Kuru Kuru Kuru
It's so cute!
It's a cat, right?
And Leo, you know, he's blue and red and white.
He's white, so he looks really good.
Isn't he cute?
He's so cute!
You scared me. Thank you.
I was hoping to bring him today.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, and one more thing... is there anything in there that looks like Leo?
Yeah.
Oh, no.
No, wait a minute.
Wait a minute.
Let's have him do it one at a time, and then we'll cool down and think about it.
Hey...
Leo's birthday.
No.
It's Leo's favorite.
I see.
That, too.
What? Why?
I was thinking mainly of the opposite.
What about the sunglasses?
You know how Hitaka's been wearing sunglasses lately?
I want you and Hitaka to wear the same ones.
Leo has a pair of men's sunglasses, too.
Oh, really?
The shape is...
They're cute.
They're so cute.
Very cute.
Are you cool? Is it cool?Are you cool? Are you hot?
I'm pretty hot. You're hot?
Yeah, I'm a little bit... I'm a little bit of a go-getter with the boys.
Well, he's a boy. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. I'll take a picture.
Yeah, I'll take pictures. I'll take pictures and I'll send them both on.
Both of them. This one. Oh, my God.
But you're right, I probably won't get the same present as Leo's.
No, they don't. You know, they did it before with the bowls.
That's right, that's right, that's right.
Hitoka's dog.
They won't cover. Right.
The last one...
Is this me?
Oh, now you're here.
That's great!
That's great.
What?
You look the happiest.
No, I just thought it'd be perfect for downstairs.
I thought it was the perfect mess.
Read it.
The Talking Confession Box.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, so I was wondering if you could recreate that one.
I want someone to recreate it. Can I do it now?
I think it already sounds. Press the button.
Press the flower part.
A beautiful woman...
Here we go.
Are you okay?
Visual code.
Okay, here we go.
I like Della. Come with me.
That's great.Amazing.
You're so cute.
It's okay.
I got it.
It's okay. Thank you, Pew.
Thank you very much. Thank you.
I'll take this as an example every day.
Why don't you take it to Indonesia?
It'll cheer you up.
Here.
I recorded Pew's voice.
I should have used that version, too.
Thanks.
He's so cute.
I'm so happy. Thank you.
I'm glad you want to wave.
Thank you.
Next.
Okay, Dad.
I was soooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooooo worried.
Dad, it really hurts.
Cute.
What did you say?
In my dream, Hito-chan appeared,
Hito-chan said she wanted an aquarium.
An aquarium?
I wanted to make an aquarium, but the moment I saw this,
I thought Hito-chan was cute,
Hito-chan came out.
Thank you.
It's cute.
I wonder.
From here.From this side.
From here.
I'm happy to just talk about this one.
It's really an aquarium.
What's that? He wants to keep fish at the entrance.
Yes, that's right.
For a moment, I thought it was an aquarium.
I don't know what it is.
But it looks cute.
I hope you'll use it someday.
It's cute.
Ah!
Huddle.
What!
Cute.
What what what what
What's cute?
Aww. Cute.
Cute.
Cute. Cute.
Cute. Cute. Cute.
I like it.
Cute.
I like this one, too.
Cute. Cute.
He's so cute.
He's an angel.You're an angel!
Everything is so cute!
I don't know.
Which one opens?
This one open?
Oh, sorry, it opens this way.
Oh, no, it's coming down a little bit.
I have a feeling it's going to come up on the left.
Wait a minute. Are you sure?
How do we get this open?
From that side. Down, down, down.
What?
This is the top.
Oh, so that's how it's supposed to be.
That's cute.
Do it.
I'll get you one someday.
I can't buy it.
It's so cute.
If I take it out, I won't be able to bring it back.
It's taped shut.
May I ask you to take a picture of it from above?
Just carry it around for a minute.
I'm sure you know who I am. I'm pretty famous.
It's a strawberry cake.
It's cute.
So pretty.
I want some now.
I can't.
It's so pretty.
I'll take it home.I'll take it home with me.
It's so cute.
Feels good.
You okay? - Yeah.
Can I show you?
It's been a little while since the last time.
You're right.
You're cute.
It's nice to see you smile. Thank you.
Cute.
I'm so happy.
It's like strawberry mousse.
Like mousse.
It's cute.
Here you go.
That's great.
Two in position.
Oh, oh, oh.
Awesome.
Oh, I...
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
No, no, no.
A-ha-ha
I did it.
Yay! Thank you.
Let's get up there, shall we?
Let's go.
It's huge!
It's so big.
It's so big!I'm big!
It's so big!
I can't see Hitachan.
I want you to use Heang Lei
I want you to take me to Indonesia.
What the hell?
What is it?
What's this?
It's cute.
From a Chilia point of view.
Chilia.
What the hell?
It was slippery.
LOL.
It was cute.
Tissue collar.
I wish you could take me anywhere.
Indonesia.
This is Indonesia?
Okay. - Okay.
Okay, let's make the plane look like this.
It's cute.
I'm gonna put some tissues in there.
I'm going to wear something cool, and this is what I'm going to wear on the plane.
Put on your sun class.
It's super nice.
It's a good cushion.
It's comfortable.
It's cute.
He's cute.
He's got a cute face.
That's the one that's smashed.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.oh, yes!
extras!
Lots of extras in this issue!
Delicious!
Unajou's Bird Scent
I think I'll go in today.
I like the scent of Unajou.
I'll take it to Indonesia.
Una, I'm taking it to Indonesia.
Julia's in Indonesia.
She wants you to feel it.
Indonesia is cute.
It's delicious.
It's so cute.
Soft and fluffy.
It's nice.
It's cute.
You want me to bring it? That way.
Kanami had crab soup.
But Yuuka had eels.
You had this, too.
If you bring it, you'll be there.
OK.
Thank you.
Buy some.
I'll give it to you.
I thought the Una Decennial was in there.
Just the Una Decade is fine.
Rast?
Yes, Rust.
Oh, okay.
Ta-da!
What? What?
What do you think? How does it feel?What do you think? How does it feel?
What?
Just a little boyoity.
Bye-bye.
What?
What is it?
What's that? Album?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah, ah
We've been together so long.
Nine years, eight years, a memory album
I thought I'd make a memory album.
Oh, yeah?
That's great.
I'm glad.
You know Pete's going camping in America, right?
So it's something you can use for that kind of thing.
Thank you.
Also...
I didn't take Akane-chan with me, I hate bugs.
I'm just trying to keep all kinds of bugs away with this Akane-chan riding around.
Really?
Really, really, really.
Because, there was a time when Ryang-chan put on Neo-Queen during the samba.
Surely, there is something similar to Rio-chan and so on.
And a hat?
Yes!
On the head of Rio-kun's hat.
He wears a hat?
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Oh, my God!
That's great!
Okay!
But I'm so happy about this.
You're so happy?So happy?
I'm so happy!
I know this!
I've never done it before.
Fireworks?
Yeah.
The color of the firelight changes.
There are seven different colors of firelight.
I've always wanted to try this.
I'm so happy!
It looks like I can go in like this.
I see.
I'm so happy! I'd be happy if you could do it at camp!
Hot sandwich make-up. I don't think I've ever seen hot sandwich make-up in this shape.
Oh, really? There are so many different kinds.
Yeah, I'll just leave something out.
I have a lot of stuff that I'm gonna run out of.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. There's a lot of these.
What's this one called?
You mean like a moxie? It's like a "mise-en-scène".
It's the one that looks good.
Thank you. I'll use it!
I've been baking eggs in breadcrumbs.
And I heard you can do it in a frying pan or something.
Wow, that's nice.
This part's detachable.
Oh, wow.
So I can use it for all kinds of things.
Thank you very much.
You can use it. Do it.
Come on, guys. Let's go.
I'm doing a lot of stuff.
I'm gladGlad to hear it.
I've been doing a lot of stuff.
I thought I'd see if there were any ushers.
I didn't see anyone.
I'm here. I'm here.
I wondered if you were here, too.
Thank you. Thank you.
Thank you.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations.
Well, thank you all for your many prayers tomorrow.
Yes, sir.
Let's do a commemorative scrub together at the end, shall we?
Let's do a commemorative scrub.
Solo first?
Yes.
Do you have that, 22?
Yes, I have it.
Oh, this way.
I don't know who that is.
The sound of flowers.
That's a nice sound.
Yes, it is.
Nice. Flashy, flashy.
Cute.
Beha beha.
I want a drink of water.
Oh, the cup.
There's a glass in the picture.
Oh, here it is.
It's over.
Phone call.
It smells like home.Smell it at home.
It's almost 8:30.
Okay, four of us.
You want to take a picture of all of us?
Yes, ma'am.
What?
Are you talking to me like I'm your mother?
Is that okay?
Chekki, chekki, chekki, chekki.
Let's get a Cheki Cheki.
That's the one. That's the one you're supposed to win.
You can win one of my videos on TikTok, with my special music.
If you make a video on TikTok...
Here we go.
Here we go. Cheese.
Yes, cheese.
Yes, how many?
Two.
Yes, cheese.
Thank you very much.
These are not the goods when I just took them.
The cheki is called Hito-chan Birthday Pick Top Project.
on the pick top by Tuesday, January 8th.
using the music of TOKISEN
If you upload Hito-chan's guess video
And hashtag super...
Hashtag Hito-chan's Birthday with the hashtag
We will draw 6 winners from those who uploaded
We will give away chekis to 6 winners!
Please upload as many videos as you can!
Please let us make a cute memorial!Please let us make a cute memorial!
Please take a look!
Yes, and finally, Hito-chan has one last thing to say.
What the heck, what the heck, what the heck...
I've had many birthdays since I was born, and every time I get older
I feel as if the number of people celebrating my birthday is increasing with each passing year.
I feel like the number of people who celebrate my birthday is increasing every year, and that makes me very happy.
I am 22 years old now, and I feel like I'm getting stronger on the inside.
I want to polish up my inner self
I will continue to do my best to polish my inner self and to create a stage where everyone can enjoy my live performances without being intimidated,
I will continue to do my best so that I can create a stage that everyone can enjoy without being intimidated.
Keep supporting us!
You will be cheering for us!
Congratulations!
So, thank you for watching the distribution.
And...,
And,
Super Tokimeki Advertising Department in at Rokohama Arena
Ticket information will be released today.
Oh!
Yes, the fastest first-come, first-served advance for the Chotokimeki Advertising Department will be
July 30, noon.
The first-come, first-served advance tickets will be available on July 30, 12:00 noon. Please check our website for more information.
Thank you all for your cooperation.
Please come, everyone. We'll be waiting for you.
Absolutely.
We'll be waiting for you.
Okay, so thank you very much for watching.
After this, the HITO-CHAN channel will be uploading a video like the HITO-CHAN birthday commemorative trip video that I mentioned earlier at around 9:00 p.m.
When this streaming is over,
After this streaming, I will be uploading the video of the song I tried singing earlier and the idol's song I tried singing on the students' official channel.
So, thank you very much for watching and congratulating us today.
Congratulations!
There's more to come.There was more...
Pasqueramoon series still to come!
To be continued!
See you on YouTuber!
See you soon!
Thank you very much.